Guide to the Nathaniel Tarn Papers, ca. 1939-2000 M1132
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4. Audio-Visual Materials
  - Naropa Seminar 3-10-90 N.T. (1) (Box 138, Folder 29)
    Autoanthropology class [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - Naropa Seminar 3-10-90 N.T. (2) (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - Naropa Seminar 3-10-90 N.T. [3?] (Box 138, Folder 31)
  - N. Tarn: Class at U. of Prague, 4/30/91 (Box 138, Folder 32)
    With M. Holub and J. Hanus[90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - N. Tarn: Class at U. of Prague, 4/30/91 (Box 138, Folder 33)
  - N. Tarn: CUNY, 12/10/76 (Box 138, Folder 34)
    Redfield Lecture[90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - N.T.: Interview at Rutgers, end '84 [1] (Box 138, Folder 35)
    Interviewed by L. Murphy, J. O'Donnell [?] [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - N.T.: Interview at Rutgers, end '84 [2?] (Box 138, Folder 36)
  - N.T.: Interview at Rutgers, end '84 [3?] (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - N.T. on diaspora 8/20/76 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    Alaskan native arts: Tarn on "diaspora;" Ed Dorn, 8/21/76 [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - N.T. Interview KPFA Los Angeles 11/8/86 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    The Poetry Connection, Wanda Coleman/ Austin Strauss [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - N.T. KLSK Interview 2/8/87 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    Deb. Bluestone/NT. (Santa Fe) [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - Nathaniel KLSK '89/June (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - N Tarn on WEVL Radio, Memphis TN 3/8/92 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    w. Lindsay Hill and Joy Tremewan [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - N Tarn: Interview by Aldo Martin for Gazet Van Antwerpen, 5/27/93 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Tarn: Radio 3, Belgium (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Tarn 1/A [No other information, possibly continuation of Radio 3, Belgium] (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - Tarn 2/A [No other information, possibly continuation of Radio 3, Belgium] (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Tarn 3/A [No other information, possibly continuation of Radio 3, Belgium] (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Tarn 3/B, 4 [No other information, possibly continuation of Radio 3, Belgium] (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Side 1: Black Mountain - 55; Beautiful Contradictions, Interview with Geo. MacBeth BBC Third - end; Side 2: - 42: R. Duncan - N Tarn interview (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - Poetry Center, London, 8/24/73 (Box 139, Folder 14)
    Tarn: Lyrics for the Bride of God [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - Poetry Center, London, 8/24/73 (Box 139, Folder 15)
    Tarn [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - N. Tarn: Account of conference on Native American arts and literature in the future, Sitka Alaska, 12/3-5/75 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Tarn: Native arts and literature, Sitka Alaska, 12/3-5/75 (cont.) (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - NT in French, Spring '76 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - NT 6/76 (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - N Tarn, Albuquerque, Downtown Center, 3/22/81 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Nathaniel Tarn, 5/1/85 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - N. T. Cody's 4/30/1986 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - Michel DeGuy/ N. Tarn reading U. Texas, Austin, 10/9/86 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Nathaniel Tarn NPC [National Poetry Center] 11/9/86 (Box 139, Folder 24)
  - Tucson Festival 3/90 (1) (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - Tucson Festival 3/90 (2) (Box 139, Folder 26)
    Tarn Talk, R. Creeley Workshop [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - Tucson Festival 3/90 (3) (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - N. Tarn: Nashville C.D. 8/27/94 (1) (Box 139, Folder 28)
    Spoken Engine [90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - Luigi: Call from Marsilio: 4/29/97 (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - [Marsilio, both sides] (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - Archaeology & Elegy: The Lyrical Impulse..(N. Tarn) (Box 139, Folder 31)
  - Natasha Tarn: Multitude of one, original reading at San Francisco State (Box 139, Folder 32)
    This is the original reading or a trial (or 2 trials) of same. An early version since tightened. Reading by Nathaniel T is too fast because of desire to get it all in.[90 minute 4-track cassette]
  - "I think this must be Eden" non-mastered (Box 139, Folder 33)
  - Tarn reads Nerval (Box 139, Folder 34)
  - N.T. Fragments (Box 139, Folder 35)
  - Poems and "Sound" Poems, St John's, July 29 (1) (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - Poems and "Sound" Poems, St John's, July 29 (2) (Box 139, Folder 37)
  - USC #11. Analogues/ Intersections: "Dr. Jekyll, Anthropologist etc." N. Tarn (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Tarn-Rodney: Reading Alashka, Bard College, 2/24/76 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Tarn/Rodney: WXPN Philadelphia (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Archive for New Poetry - UCSD (SPL - 1100) N. Tarn and J. Rodney reading 11/6/91 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Scott Mahler (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - Musical setting of N.T. Macchu Picchu (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - Nicaragua sounds NT (1) (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Nicaragua sounds NT (2) (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Before the snake, demos (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - We magazine xv (Box 140, Folder 10)
    [Professionally produced 90 minute 4-track cassette, no performances by Tarn]
  - Six Poets, Fish Drum #7, Santa Fe (Box 140, Folder 11)
    [Professionally produced 90 minute 4-track cassette, Tarn reads: Home 4,6,7 (all appeared in Conjunctions), Architexture 1(Temblor)]
  - Strick: Song of the Andoumboulou 16-25, Nathaniel Mackey with Royal Hartigan and Hafez Modirzadeh (Box 140, Folder 12)
    [Professionally produced compact disc]
  - Sergey Kuryokhin: Some combination of fingers and passion (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Maxine Hong Kingston: The dance of the golden world (Box 140, Folder 14)
    [Spoken Engine, professionally produced compact disc]
  - Nathaniel Tarn: I think this may be Eden (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - Music from "the Postman" (Il Postino) [featuring the poems of Pablo Neruda] (Box 140, Folder 16)
    [Miramax, Hollywood Records, professionally produced compact disc]
  - Nathaniel Tarn, Janet Rodney, Telluride Institute, Talking Gourds Fest, Cloud House Poetry Archive (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - Nathaniel Tarn reading at Living Batch, Albuquerque, June 22, 1990 (Box 140, Folder 18)
    [Video by Lee Bartlett]
  - Tarn '53, Marte Albair[sp?] (Box 141, Folder 1)
    [16 mm super-x Kodak movie film]
  - Tarn '53, Kabah, Uxuial (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Tarn '53, Copan, D (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Tarn '53, Chuirigua[sp?], Tikal (blocked), Mitla (blocked) (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Poetry Now 12/19/66 "Mahler" (Box 141, Folder 5)
    [Scotch "150" magnetic tape, 3" reel, 3ins, 300ft]
  - BBC Third Programme: "The king, the traitor and the cross," E.M. Mendelson, 2/7/57 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    [Emitape magnetic tape, 3" reel, 3-3/4ins, 99m?]
  - British Council Tape # 996, Contemporary Poets reading their own poems: Nathaniel Tarn, selections from Old Savage/ Young City, Penguin Modern Poets No. 7, and unpublished works, 10/20/65 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    [Emitape magnetic tape, 5" reel, 3-3/4ins, tape duration 28' 55"]
  - British Council Tape # 997, The Poet Speaks: Nathaniel Tarn talks to Gillian Dickinson, 10/20/65 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    [Emitape magnetic tape, 5" reel, 3-3/4ins, tape duration 20' 20"]
  - [Unidentified] (Box 141, Folder 9)
    [Scotch "200" magnetic tape, speed unknown, 1200,' 5" reel]
  - The Dinner, Tarn plays Niels Bohr (Box 141, Folder 10)
    [Demo tape]
  - Temple University Faculty Series: Creative Writing, Nathaniel Tarn reading, 4/3/92 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    [60 minute duration]
  - Santiago Atitlan, 1952-1953, Mendelson (Box 142, Folder 1)
    [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Santiago Atitlan, 1952-1953, Mendelson (Box 142, Folder 2)
    N. Chivilio, end of S. Antonio, J.Sigay, S. Sigay, D. Pop[?] [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Santiago Atitlan, 1952-1953, Mendelson (Box 142, Folder 3)
    Dedication of candles[?]/ San Juan praying for San Pedrano[?][Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Santiago Atitlan, 1952-1953, Mendelson (Box 142, Folder 4)
    Church, 1/2 way through last side: begins San Antonio [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Santiago Atitlan, 1952-1953, Mendelson (Box 142, Folder 5)
    Civilio praying for Miguel Sol [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Santiago Atitlan, 1952-1953, Mendelson (Box 142, Folder 6)
    San Juan Colombia Fiesta [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Pat - London Xmas tape sent to me in Burma; review by Philip Hobs[bawm?] of Old Savage, BBC 16/1/65 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Before Burma 1958, BBC Programs (Box 142, Folder 8)
    Pat and Michael sing song folk tunes of the South; BBC Third 11/12/64, Ginsburg, Hobsbawm, Lucie-Smith, Baldwin, Scannell[and others - writing undecipherable, see photocopy enclosed with box]; track 2: David Wevill, Living Poet, BBC third, 31/10/64 [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - BBC, the Poet's Voice, 1962-1963 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    The poet's Voice Third Programme, 17/11/62: N.Tarn, P.Porter, S. Plath, and George MacBeth, commentary; 6/5/63: Drafts of Simeon Bar Yochai and To Tell [?] of the Ile de France, The problem of Style (recorded 11/5/65), the Omen; Track Two: The Poet's Voice, BBC Third, 15/5/63, 10:35 - 11:5, John Silkin, P. Hobsbawm, P. Redgrove, Ted Walker, Keith [?], Nathaniel Tarn [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - BBC recordings, circa 1963 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    Tarn: Track 1: recording of full six BBC Messianic poems; A. Waley: Track 1: [?] on BBC Third; Tarn: Track 2: BBC "Group Evening" Broadcast 9-10 pm 23/8/63 [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - BBC, The Poet's Voice, 1/3/64; 2/16/64 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    1. The Poet's Voice including Tarn: Prayer for Roses; L. MacNeice, Souvenirs d'eu/[?]; 2. Jon Silkin, The Living Poet 3/1/64; The Poet's Voice including Tarn: Noah on Ararat Again [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Radio Broadcasts, 1964 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    Alvarez/ Sylvia Plath Memorial Programme: portion of conversation, the little magazine: MacBeth, Silkin, Bax[?], Riddell with mention of N.T.; interview at Prog. National, Radio Belge, with Marcel [?], at E. Lucie Smith 21/2/64, broadcast 24/2/64 at 9:15 pm; Charles Tomlinson, the Living Poet 8/3/64; Alvarez - Hughes reading Polish; 2 Herbert 26/4/64 (partial) [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - 1. Mandalay Arts School 2. Tom Gunn "Misanthpopos" BBC Third 8/3/65 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    1. Orchestral not[?] songs, oboe song and solo flute [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Brecht selections, Jan. 66 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    1. Brecht Selections, Third, Jan. 66; 2 Giacometti talks to D. Sylvester [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Neruda, Macchu Picchu (Box 143, Folder 7)
    Neruda Macchu Picchu, Cohen - Tarn, BBC 3rd; [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Neruda reading (Box 143, Folder 8)
    Neruda reading; JM Cohen: Auh-poetry 2 with Tarn poems and commentaries [Magnetic tape, 5" reel]
  - Gary Snyder, 4/14/70 #1 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    3-3/4 ips full track [Magnetic tape, 7" reel]
  - Gary Snyder, 4/14/70 #2 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Nathaniel Tarn, Library of Congress Recording Laboratory (Box 144, Folder 3)
    Studio "B" on 3/23/71, tracks D.T., 7.5"/second ips mono [Magnetic tape, 7" reel]
  - Dante, Seminar #1, 9/20/71 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    [Magnetic tape, 7" reel]
  - [Dante, Seminar #2?] (Box 144, Folder 5)
    [See original notes on cardboard sheet included with container; Magnetic tape, 7" reel]
  - [unidentified, possibly Dante, Seminar #3] (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - [unidentified, possibly more Dante Seminar; see sheet with original notes inside container] (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - 2 is 1, 29 November 1971[?] (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Nathaniel Tarn reading at Bard College, 15 May 1974 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - 1. Post-Romantic 2. Thematic Poetry [n.d.] (Box 145, Folder 2)
    [1200', 1.5 mylar, magnetic tape, 7" reel]
  - SLF, Tarn and Hollo #1 [n.d.] (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - SLF, Tarn and Hollo #2 [n.d.] (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - [Unidentified] (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - [Unidentified] (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - [Unidentified] (Box 145, Folder 7)
- Series 5. Accession 2006-011
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains correspondence, diaries, various drafts, poems, reviews, and ephemera.
  - General correspondence/miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General correspondence/miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General correspondence/miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General correspondence/miscellaneous, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Drafts (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Poems in Webzines (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reviews, etc. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Salt Book 3 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Salt Book 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Salt Book 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anthropology (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Anthropology (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Paul Harbaugh (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Notes Towards an Anthropological Course (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Older Unpublished Prose (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Older Unpublished Prose (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - J.P. Auxemery: translation of "Scandals" correspondence (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - J.P. Auxemery: translations of Nathanial Tarn poems, correspondence (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lee Bartlett (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Daniel Bouchard (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Paul Christensen (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Peter Cole (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Christopher Daniels (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Michel DeGuy (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Richard Deming (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Kurt Devrese (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Joseph Donahue (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Theodore Enslin (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Frank Ettenberg (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Forrest Gander (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Michael Heller (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Brenda Hillman (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lindsay Hill (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Kenneth Way (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Eddin Khoo (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Hector Manjarrez (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Nathanial Mackey (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Sarah Menefee (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Peter O'Leary (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Geoffrey O'Brien (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Toby Olson (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Dennis Phillips (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Peter Quarterman (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Jerome Rothenberg (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Roberto Tejada (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Hans Ten Berge (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - John Tranter (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Eliot Weinberger (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Peter Lamborn Wilson (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Arnold Wesker (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - John L. Wright (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Heriberto Yepez (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Zhang Ziqing (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Danish Newspaper, October 29, 2004 re. Tarn (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Prof. Moffit/Jospeh Beuys (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Shamoon Zamir (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Diary, 1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Blitz records August-September, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Diary, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Diary, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Diary, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Notepad Clifton-Cambridge, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Notepad early Cambridge, [1946?] (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Diary, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Paris Diary, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Notebook: "Ballet," 1943-1948 (Flat-box 6)
  - Diary, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Notebook (French), 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Diary (French), November 1948 - April 1948 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Diary (French), May 1949 - September 1949 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Diary (French), Septmber 1949 - May 1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Addresses, circa 1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Notebook (French), 1949 - 1951 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Kew Gardens (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Notebook (birds), 1940's/1970's (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Diary (French), July 1950 - January 1951 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Diary (French), January 1951 - August 1951 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Diary (French), August 1951 - March 1952 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Diary (French), March 1952 - July 1952 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Diary remnants, 1953, 1954, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Notebook, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Daybook, October 1953 - April 1958 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Notebook, 195[3 or 4] - 1955 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, 1955 - [1956?] (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Diaries, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Diaries, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Diary, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Diary, early 1958 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Diary, late 1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Burma daybook, May 1958 - November 1959 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Notebook, June 1958 - October 1961 (turns into diary April 1960) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Diary, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Daybook, January 1960 - January 1963 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Notebook, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Diary, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Notebook, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Daybook, January 1963 - February 1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Notebook, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Diary, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Sicily, 1966, with drawings (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Occassional sketches, August 1966 - July 1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Daybook, February 1966 - April 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Notebook, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Havana notebook, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Daybook, April 1968 - June 1970 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Wall Calendar, 1973 (Flat-box 14, Folder 1)
  - Wall Calendar, 1974 (Flat-box 14, Folder 2)
  - Wall Calendar, 1975 (Flat-box 14, Folder 3)
  - Wall Calendar, 1976 (Flat-box 14, Folder 4)
  - Wall Calendar, 1977 (Flat-box 14, Folder 5)
  - Wall Calendar, 1978 (Flat-box 14, Folder 6)
  - Wall Calendar, 1979 (Flat-box 14, Folder 7)
  - John Digby: early collages, 2005 (Flat-box 14, Folder 8)
  - Jargon 82: Who is Little Enis?, by Jonathan Williams (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Annie Wobbler (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Daybook, October 2000 - April 2003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Daybook, April 2003- December 2005 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Talisman (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Sarawak, Borneo 2005 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Sarawak, Borneo 2005, continued (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - "26" including poem by Tarn (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Series 6. Accession 2011-046
  Series 6 consists of correspondence, ephemera, photographs, poems, materials relating to both Scandals in the House of Birds and Avia, CDs, books, and assorted serials.
  - Correspondence and Ephemera
    - Adamson, Robert, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Adamson, Robert/J. Gemes, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Adamson, Robert/J. Gemes, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Adamson, Robert/J. Gemes, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Adamson, Robert/J. Gemes, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Anania, Michael, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Anthropology, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Anthropology, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Anthropology, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Anthropology, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Anthropology, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Australia, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Auxemery, J.P., 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Auxemery, J.P., 2007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Auxemery, J.P., 2008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Auxemery, J.P., 2009 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Auxemery, J.P., 2010 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer and Lee, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer and Lee, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer and Lee, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer and Lee, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer and Lee, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Bei, Dao, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Ten Berge, Hans, 2006, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Ten Berge, Hans, 2009 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Ten Berge, Hans, 2010, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Bouchard, Daneil, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bouchard, Daniel, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bouchard, Daniel, 2008 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bouchard, Daniel, 2009, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Bouchard, Daniel, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Caddy, David, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Caddy, David, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Campbell, Carolee/Ninja Press, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Campbell, Carolee/Ninja Press, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Campbell, Carolee/Ninja Press, 2009, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Cerise Press, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Christensen, Paul, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Deguy, Michel, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Deguy, Michel, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Deguy, Michel, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Deguy, Michel, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Deming, Richard, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Deming, Richard, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Deming, Richard, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Deming, Richard, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Deming, Richard, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Digby, John, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Digby, John, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Digby, John, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Donahue, Joseph, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Donahue, Joseph, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Donahue, Joseph, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Donahue, Joseph, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Donahue, Joseph, 2010, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Economou, George, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Enslin, Ted, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Fong-Wust, Monique, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Fong-Wust, Monique, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Gander, Forrest, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - General, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - General, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - General, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - General, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - General, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - General, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - General, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - General, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - General, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - General, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - General, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - General, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - General, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - General, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - General, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - General, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - General, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - General, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - General, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - General, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - General, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Gergely, Agnes, 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Gervitz, Susan, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Heller, Michael, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Heller, Michael/J. Augustine, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Heller, Michael/J. Augustine, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Heller, Michael/J. Augustine, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Heller, Michael, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Hill, Barry, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Hill, Barry, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Hill, Lindsay, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Hill, Lindsay, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Hill, Lindsay, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Hillman, Brenda, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Hillman, Brenda, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Hillman, Brenda, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Hillman, Brenda, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Hillman, Brenda, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Irby, Ken, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Irby, Ken, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Kearns, Cleo McNelly, 2006, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Kearns, Cleo McNelly, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Kearns, Cleo McNelly, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Kearns, Cleo McNelly, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Khoo, Eddin, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Khoo, Eddin, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Khoo, Eddin, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Kuhl, Nancy, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - De Lacerda, Alberto, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Lewis, Ruark, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Lewis, Ruark, 2009, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Lewis, Ruark, 2010, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Manjarrez, Hector, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Matthias, John, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Matthias, John, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Menefee, Sarah, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Metropolitan Opera, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous E-mail Printouts, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Morrow, Bradford, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - O'Brien, Geoffrey, 2006, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - O'Brien, Geoffrey, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - O'Brien, Geoffrey, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Olson, Toby, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Olson, Toby, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Olson, Toby, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Olson, Toby, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 8)